Hey, wake up. It's nearly time for class to start. Mr. Yasuda? Don't say I didn't try, at least.
Let's go. We gotta hurry and get back before the bell rings.
Whoa. Yasuda's out.
Huh?
His hair is, like, crazy smooth and soft.
Stylin'.
Yasuda. Mr. Yasuda!
Was there someone behind me just a second ago?
Yep. Pretty sure they were senior students.
I have a feeling they were girls, too. And I miss them.
So, uh...
My class has started without me. Damn it.
Um, just so you're aware...
Aware of what?
It's your head. There's something wrong with it.
Yes, every day!
Huh?
But why'd you bring that up now, of all times? Can't you see I'm in a rush here?
You misunderstood, yet you're still correct.
Ah, I've got a class to teach.
I've got a class to teach.
But why how'd you bring that up now, of all times?
Likeanyone rien to do...
harderons...
That long, although I didn't understand,
Because it's just being used to by the reunifications...
Thank you.
Seriously, is this a joke to you?
He's wondering if we're joking?
Question.
So, um...
Do it?
Ask him, Hori.
It's not worth mentioning.
Well, your English score was as awesome as ever, Hori.
Uh, um, thank you?
Come on, brain, think of something to say.
Does that bother you?
No.
Sir?
Let me guess.
Need a potty break?
No.
But...
Ask him.
I believe in you.
The theme.
Um, what theme?
Theme for today.
Today has a theme?
Does this have anything at all to do with our discussion regarding exam grades, Miyamura?
Uh, no, sir.
It doesn't.
Spectacular.
Then sit.
All right, what's up?
You appear to be very distracted and confused.
It's all your fault.
I just had to go and oversleep.
What class are we on now anyway?
I'm sorry for being late.
Forgive me.
Ah, decided to grace us with your presence, huh?
Oh.
Okay, you're going to have to stop.
I can't live you this early, Yasuna.
Really?
I look dying.
Oh, my gosh.
Too funny.
Were you still, like, going to execute today or what, Yasuna?
What?
You all think I look cute?
Do you want to explain why?
Miss Lou, face your eyes.
The heck is this?
Teens, I swear.
If girls are going to play with my hair, I should be conscious.
I want to feel a gentle touch of their fingers while I'm wide awake.
There really is something wrong with this head.
Wasted opportunity.
Hey, Mr. Ajima.
You know where the reference room key disappeared, too?
I don't.
Try asking the one who's in charge of it.
And who would this fabled keeper of keys be?
Nakamine, last I checked.
In fact, I believe he used that room himself just yesterday.
Mr. Nakamine.
Will you please return the reference room key?
I did.
It should be hanging up where all the other keys are.
Nope.
It ain't there.
But I put it back.
It's not there.
That's so weird.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Oh, my bad, man.
Guess it's been stuck in my coat pocket since yesterday.
Why is this scatterbrain in charge of anything, let alone keys?
Well, I'm glad we found it.
You really are some kind of keeper of keys.
Oops.
Wait.
It's the key to my bike lock that I thought I lost over summer break.
Back during the summer?
That was two seasons ago.
Thanks.
I really owe you one.
Now I can ride my bicycle again.
Good for you.
But I didn't do anything.
What a modest guy.
Maybe we should entrust the key to somebody else.
Did you block in any other keys you forgot about?
Hmm.
That's a good question.
Hey, it's Yasuda.
What's the other dude's name?
Mr. Nakamine.
He's the physics teacher.
Did that lab coat come with trick pockets?
Looked straight up magical.
That's a lot of keys you have on you.
Yeah, it's quite a few.
Not magic, though.
I could also pull a crap ton of keys out of my pockets, you guys.
This isn't a competition so you can tone down the aggression.
I know.
I'm just saying.
I could do that.
You missed one.
Must have dropped it before.
Good eye.
You just saved me a lot of trouble.
It's probably the key to something pretty important.
Uh-oh.
I'm not sure where the reference room key is now.
Mr. Nakamine?
Huh?
Oh.
Wait up!
Hmm?
You dropped all these.
Oh, gosh.
I didn't even notice.
Thank you so much.
Wow.
You're welcome.
But you might have a hole in your pocket.
Nah.
This coat's really sturdy, so...
Oh.
No worries.
I just happened to have a sewing kit with me.
Well, well.
You're quite skilled with your hands, young lady.
Young lady?
I'm Ushikawa from Class 3-1, sir.
Oh.
Right.
I'm sorry.
You know, to be fair, I don't teach Class 3-1.
True, but you did teach us when we were first years here.
Am I ringing any bells?
Ever since I was about knee-high, I've been terrible at remembering faces and names.
That said, I actually do remember you.
Hmm?
Hmm.
He-he-he.
An affair?
It should have been me in there.
Gosh darn that man's ditzy charm.
How?
How'd he get a teenage girl to sit in a closed room with him?
No clue.
Now shut the hell up and die, loser.
Casually demanding that people die is wrong.
You almost sounded like a real teacher for a second.
Gotta say, a sewing kit's the last thing I would expect someone as breezy as Yoshikawa
to have stowed in her school bag.
Well, that goes double for me.
Because...
Toru, where's your button, dude?
Oh, I didn't even notice.
Looks sloppy.
Make sure you sew on a new one.
Yep.
No help.
Me and my button-less cover left a fit for ourselves.
It sounds like she has zero love for you, man.
No different from some random lunkhead she passes on the street.
You don't know what's going on in that cute, kooky head of hers, so quit acting like you do, perv!
Hey!
Nakamine's the person who got her alone in the room!
Hate on him!
I can't detect the slightest scent of ulterior motives, criminality, or indecency from Nakamine.
You, on the other hand...
I'll have you know that my intentions come from a pure and wholesome place!
Ball!
You did it so fast, and it's such amazing craftsmanship!
From now on, come to me if you get holes in your clothes.
And take better care of those keys.
Just wondering, but...
Do you always have a needle and thread handy?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
There's this guy I know who keeps losing his buttons left and right.
His dumb face doesn't tell me when it happens, though.
He's missing out on some first-rate tailoring.
Hey, thirsty?
How about I treat you to a drink to show my gratitude?
Thanks, but I'm still working on my peach tea.
Oh!
Know what I want?
Show me your hand.
Huh?
What are they talking about?
Again, no clue.
She finished sewing.
Now leave!
Tohru?
Well, well.
So, um, what were you doing back there?
Hm?
With his hands?
Yeah.
Indeed, huh?
I read his palm.
No!
Since when do you read palms?
Since recently, because it's neat.
Want me to read yours, too?
Nah, I think I'll pass.
Why?
Not like I'm mine.
Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Your lines are super-duper mega-faint!
Mr. Nakamine's are the exact same!
Wait, that counts as a reading?
I thought you would say how lucky I am and stuff.
How am I supposed to know that?
Go check your daily horoscope.
Talk about a total cop-out.
Well, anyway, have you tried reading anyone else's palm yet?
Nope.
Oh, except for Hody.
Nice big and bold lines.
Why'd you ask?
Because people might think you're a weirdo.
Not that I do, though.
Wait, so getting into a hobby like fortune-telling makes me weird in here?
No!
Plenty of people read palms.
It's fun, not weird.
I know, I know.
Yo, Ishikawa!
Good news!
Miyamura says he's in for tomorrow.
All right!
Now, where should we do this?
I suggest we find an empty classroom, my old chum.
Don't call me chum.
I want in on the secret, too!
Oh, you know.
Just a little bro-tastic bro-fun!
Sounds dumb.
Really?
I had a hard time sneaking in here.
Huh?
Oh, that thing is colossal.
Bigger is better, and we all know it.
I think looks are important, too.
No way!
Size is where the romance lies.
Hmm.
How's it hanging, adolescent boys?
Or should I say, what's got you so...
excited?
So, where you living nowadays, Yasuda?
Why ask?
You want to set it on fire?
I'm just curious.
You don't need to be curious about where your teachers live.
Besides, you three are in trouble.
You got that?
Sorry.
But, sir, I can't think of one school rule
that forbids us from eating cake inside a classroom.
Because bringing a cake that massive is unprecedented.
Oh, yeah, hey.
You live a stone's throw away from the school, don't you?
If it's the same address that I used for your New Year's card.
Ooh.
Are you planning to visit me?
Don't you dare!
And we aren't finished talking about your dumb cake!
Cake has lost our interest.
We wish to know about your lifestyle.
Jeez, you're blunt.
Do you live alone?
Well, yeah.
Suppose I do.
Got a girlfriend?
Not presently.
But why does that even matter to you?
Because you're you.
The lewd dude who raves about his love for high school girls.
If you had a normal, non-spicy lady waiting for you at home,
I'd be mad.
Non-spicy?
Yeah, I feel that.
The thought of him in an average relationship is rough.
Right?
Luckily, I'm not.
So you're safe.
For now.
But if you land a perfectly normal, non-spicy babe, tell us.
What kind of woman are you imagining?
So you don't intend to get married?
I'm lacking a partner for such an event.
Are you keeping up?
Commitment's hot.
Put a ring on your normal, non-spicy girlfriend.
Guys, who the hell are you talking about?
Though I do want to wed before Nakamine.
So?
He's uber fixated on that dude.
Damn it.
You rope me into making small talk.
I really want to see where you live, Yasuda.
Same.
You jerks aren't welcome.
Unless you come knocking with your lady friends.
Ishikawa brings Yoshikawa.
Miyamura brings Hori.
And Iyurayu bring Ayasaki and Kono.
Then piss off.
Hey, what happened to that bright-eyed enthusiasm you had mere seconds ago?
You're the all-time worst.
No New Year's card for you next year.
I wasn't expecting one.
Speaking of expectations, I'm not sure how we look to you, but Kono and Ayasaki hardly tolerate me.
Oh, I see.
Sorry.
Now, ask for the matter of the gigantic cake.
Ah.
Hmm?
Never mind.
Go back to class.
Wow, really?
Woo-hoo!
Don't worry.
We'll visit again real soon.
Great.
But whenever you do, just remember to bring me some cake, too.
All right?
Total teacher fail.
Oh, but we are coming back for the cake after school.
Will you please keep it cold for us?
You bet.
Of course I will.
What kind of experiment is this?
It's nine o'clock at night in the student council room.
The door's locked from the outside.
And there's a slumbering demon.
How could we both conk out so easily?
Is it drugs?
Did someone drug us somehow?
Well, regardless, it's best to let sleeping demons lie.
If I call the school, it should bring in the faculty office.
What?
Whoa, it's dark.
Ah, man, what time is it?
Do you know?
Time to die.
Oh, John, please don't panic.
But it seems someone locked the door while we were sleeping.
We're trapped.
Trapped?
How could you let this happen, you dummy?
Hey, you woke up a few seconds ago.
You're as much to blame as I am.
Well, this timing sucks.
I was going to buy carrots on the way home, but that's obviously out now.
I know the gardening club's growing a whole bunch of carrots.
Take some of theirs and be happy, okay?
And you call yourself our class president?
Your cell phone, call the school, or anybody.
Just hurry!
Is that how your mother taught you to ask people for help?
I'm sorry.
Please, hurry.
All right, chop chop.
What's the phone number for the school?
You should have that stored in your contact list!
Bite me.
Bet it's in the student handbook, right?
It is!
Come on!
Quit dawdling!
Why are you in such a rush, huh?
Is it because you need to use the dang bathroom, too?
Quit copying me.
It's a natural function!
Wait, you also have to go?
Honestly, what the hell are you two doing?
I was getting ready to head home, but...
Oh!
You could at least say thanks for saving us before dashing off to who knows where!
So, what kept you at school until this time of night?
He was out like a light, sir.
Now hang on.
This one was fast asleep, too.
Are you sure?
You weren't up to anything obscene, were you?
Excuse me?
Obscene?
Like what?
Freak nasty hoo-hoo-ha-ha.
Students will stay late every once in a while and get it on undisturbed.
Disgusting!
Don't let me in with all those nymphos!
And isn't this the fault of whoever locked the door to the student council room without checking inside first?
What?
Speak up.
I can't hear you, Sengoku.
You know, I do have other ways of figuring out if you were getting frisky.
Hori!
Take off all your clothes right now!
What sort of situation did I stumble upon?
Oh!
Hello, Mr. Ajima.
Thank goodness you're here!
Check Sengoku for love bites while I check Hori.
It'd be the other way.
If it wasn't purely absurd.
We'll learn everything if we can see below the belt.
All skirts and pants will be staying on.
I certainly hope you haven't used that excuse to do inappropriate things with other female students in the past.
Go home and have a good night, kids.
I need to have a word in private with this deviant, okay?
Okay!
Hang on.
Deviant is a little uncalled for, don't you think?
If you'll excuse us!
Wait!
Come back!
Now, we're going to go over this in detail.
I need to hurry home.
The hallway's freezing!
Whoa!
You got locked in the student council room?
You should have called.
I would have rushed over to let you out.
I wasn't trapped long.
It was no big deal.
Were you all alone?
Or afraid?
Neither.
Sengoku was with me.
Hmm.
You okay, Mr. President?
I heard you were stuck in a room with Hori.
Did she do anything to you?
Not this time.
I'm fine.
Hey!
Do tell what you're trying to imply.
Um!
I meant the power dynamic!
Right?
She's talking to you!
Leave me out of it!
Elaborate now, Miyamoto.
This behavior is exactly what he meant!
What?
Be calm.
Please don't resort to violence.
Deep breaths.
Have to process that anger and purge it from your soul.
It's a chance to improve yourself.
That can't be the real Yasuda.
A non-evil twin, perhaps?
No, that's the guy.
He just had a change of heart is all.
Compliments of her own Miss Tarajima.
That seemed more like a change of a person than a change of heart if you asked me!
Maybe she brainwashed him.
I love that woman!
She rocks!
Life is precious.
All- بتをñochair deriva
옳発狂ani
じゃあ、こんなの多かったよ
って見せびらかしたもの
褒めてくれた君も
前から同じの持っていたの
わぁ、今さらそんなこと
Oh